<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Hotblog</title><link>https://blog.hotseat.io/</link><description>Recent content on The Hotblog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.hotseat.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Refer the most friends to Hotseat, win a $50 Amazon gift card!</title><link>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/referrals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/referrals/</guid><description>You can now refer your friends and classmates to Hotseat! If they sign up via a unique link on your settings page and write a review, then you will both get two notification tokens!
As a bonus, we&amp;rsquo;re also running a referral contest! If you refer the most new users to Hotseat by February 1, you&amp;rsquo;ll get a $50 Amazon gift card.
The fine print:
Hotseat Referral Promotion Contest (the &amp;ldquo;Contest&amp;rdquo;) is open to legal residents of the fifty (50) United States and the District of Columbia who are at least eighteen (18) years old at the time of entry.</description></item><item><title>Hotseat Tech Talk: Scraping UCLA at Scale</title><link>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/tech-talk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/tech-talk/</guid><description>Last month, Team Hotseat partnered up with UCLA ACM to talk about the tech behind Hotseat. You can view the video below or check out the slides!</description></item><item><title>Hotseat: Back to School Edition</title><link>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/back-to-school/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/back-to-school/</guid><description>Since releasing Hotseat in June, we&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard at adding more features to make the enrollment process even more seamless. Introducing – Hotseat: Back to School Edition!
Class status texts This is the feature we&amp;rsquo;ve been most excited about. Get text messages when a class opens up or becomes full! The message will have a link that takes you directly to MyUCLA.
To get enrollment texts, you first need to head over to your settings page and add your phone number.</description></item><item><title>Announcing Hotseat!</title><link>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/announcing-hotseat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hotseat.io/posts/announcing-hotseat/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re super excited to announce Hotseat, the best way to enroll in classes at UCLA.
What’s Hotseat? Hotseat is the newest course enrollment platform. We aggregate course information from multiple sources – information like grade distributions, professor evaluations, textbook information and more – and provide it to students completely free of charge. All you need is a UCLA email address and the world of better enrollment is at your fingertips.</description></item></channel></rss>